Guide to the Rudolf Kompfner Papers
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Rudolf Kompfner papers
1937-1981
SC0194
Kompfner, Rudolf, 1909-1977
10 Linear feet (21 boxes)
The Kompfner papers span the years 1937 to 1977 and concentrate primarily on his research interests while at Bell Laboratories, Stanford University and Oxford University. The collection includes general correspondence files, diaries (1937-41), notebooks and notes (1937-77), articles and reports (1937-80), awards and drawings. Additional material received 1985 and 1987 includes correspondence, research files, notebooks, patent records, and publications.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Provenance
Gift of Peggy Kompfner 1978, 1980-85; loan from Bell Laboratories, 1979.
The Rudolf Kompfner papers, with the exception of his Bell Lab notebooks, were the gift of his wife, Peggy Kompfner to Stanford University in 1978; the materials were transferred from the Kompfner's Stanford University residence to the University Archives in that year with an addition later in the year.
In 1979, Bell Laboratories, at the request of Professor Calvin Quate, transferred 26 research notebooks regarding Kompfner's research to the Stanford University Archlves. The notebooks are on indefinite loan in accordance with the agreement dated 14 February 1979 and title to the notebooks, including literary rlghts, are retained by Bell Laboratories. No restrictions were placed on access to the notebooks, and they may be studied by researchers as part of the Rudolf Kompfner papers in the reading room of the University Archives.
Information about Access
This collection is open for research.
Biographical/Historical Sketch
Professor of Applied Physics at Stanford University and world renowned communications scientist, Rudolf Kompfner came to Stanford in 1973 after a distinguished career at Bell Telephone Laboratories, Oxford University, and with British government research.
Professor Kompfner was born in Vienna in 1909 and received the degree of engineer from the Technische Hochschule in 1933. He emigrated to England in 1934 where he worked as an architect. Kompfner already had a strong interest in experimental physics, however, and began a self-guided study of the field. He was already an accomplished research physicist when he received his Ph. D. from Oxford University, having worked at Birmingham University (1941-44) and Oxford's Clarendon Laboratory (1944-51). His invention of the traveling wave tube during this time is credited with making future satellite communications practicable. In 1950, he developed the backward wave oscillator which made microwave oscillators electronically tunable.
Ultimately the holder of over 50 patents, Kompfner continued his research at the Bell Laboratories from 1952 to 1973. His last years, 1973 to 1977, were spent in research and teaching at both Stanford University and Oxford University, focusing prlmarily on integrated optics.
Professor Kompfner received numerous awards, including the National Medal of Science in 1975 for his invention of the traveling wave tube and for major contributions to communications satellites and optical communications. He was a member of the National Academy of Science and of the American Academy of Arts and Sciences.
Description of the Collection
The Kompfner papers span the years 1937 to 1977 and concentrate primarily on his research interests while at Bell Laboratories, Stanford University and Oxford University. The collection includes general correspondence files, diaries (1937-41), notebooks and notes (1937-77), articles and reports (1937-80), awards and drawings. Additional material received 1985 and 1987 includes correspondence, research files, notebooks, patent records, and publications.
Of particular note are the 26 research notebooks compiled by Kompfner regarding his research at Bell Laboratories, 1952 to 1973 (series IV) and his 1937 diary documenting his selfdirected readings and experiments in physics while still a practicing architect (series II).
Arrangement
The collection is arranged in seven series and two additions: 1. General Files, 1941-1978; 2. Diaries, 1937-1941; 3. Notebooks and Notes, 1937-1977; 4. Bell Laboratory Notebooks, 1952-1973; 5. Articles, Reports and Speeches, 1937-1980; 6. Awards, 7. Drawings.
Access Terms
Bell Telephone Laboratories.; Benham, W. E.; English Electric Valve Co.; Fuchs, Wolfgang.; Kompfner, Rudolf, 1909-1977; Liebmann, Gerard.; Massachusetts Institute of Technology.; Stanford University. Department of Applied Physics. Faculty.; Articles.; Awards.; Backward-wave tubes.; Diaries.; Drawings.; Notebooks.; Physics--Research.; Reports.; Science--History.; Traveling-wave tubes.
Collection Contents
- General files, 1941-1978; Series I
  This series is highlighted by Kompfner's correspondence with the British Admiralty, the Bell Telephone Laboratories and the English Electric Valve Company over the years 1944-1955. This correspondence mostly concerns Kompfner's research in physics. Associated with this correspondence are a number of unpublished handwritten and typed manuscripts written during the same time span. Also included are several patent applications bearing upon Kompfner's research interests in the late 30's and early 40's.
  The series is arranged alphabetically by subject. The manuscripts are listed alphabetically by title under the category "Research Notes and Manuscripts."
  - Admiralty, 1944-1950 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Associated Universities Incorporated, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Associated Universities Incorporated, financial statements, 1977 Sep-Oct (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Bell Telephone Laboratories, 1946 Apr-1951 Dec (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Benham, W. E., correspondence with, 1941 Jul-1942 Dec (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - The Codrington Club, membership list, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - English Electric Valve Co., 1950 Aug 25-Dec 15 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - English Electric Valve Co., 1951 Jan 2-1955 Aug 10 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Fuchs, Wolfgang, correspondence with, 1941 Feb-1942 Mar (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Ginzton Laboratory, memo, 1977 Nov 30 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Helical line tube patent, 1943-1946 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Helical line tube patent, includes mss., 1947-1952 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Liebmann, Gerard, correspondence with, 1941 Feb-1942 Mar (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Loaded space tube, include mss., 1949 Mar-Jun (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology, 1951 May-Sep (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - National Academy of Engineering, Founders Award, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - National Academy of Engineering, nomination form, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - National Academy of Sciences, minutes of April 26, 1977 meeting, 1977 Nov 21 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Patent Application, "Device for the Conversion of an Image Formed by Lightrays into Electrical Impulses", 1936 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Patent Application #14041, "Discharge Tubes Making Use of the Principle of Velocity Modulation", 1940 Sep-Nov (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Patent Application #9360/41, "Generator of Electromagnetic Oscillations at Very High Frequencies", 1941 Jul-Oct (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Patent Application, "A Graphical Analysis of the Planar Whole-Anode Magnetron", 1941 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Personal correspondence, miscellaneous, 1937-1945 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Projects, miscellaneous progress reports, untitled mss. and notes, 1945-1947, Undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Research notes and mss. (by title), A-El., 1943-1951, undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - "Absorbtion of Radiation by a Gas," 3 pp., Undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - "Amplification of Plasmaoscillations by Means of D.C. Fields," 12 pp., 1951 Mar 13 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - "Design of a Collector for V.M. Detector," 24 typed pp., Undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - "Design of an Electron Gun for S-band Traveling Wave," 20 pp., Undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - "Electron Beams in Wave Guides and Transmission Lines," 48 pp., 1943 Aug (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - "Electron Multiplier as T.K. Cell," 4 typed pp., 1948 Jun 5 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Research notes, mss. and correspondence: Electron microscopy, 1939 Dec-1940 Feb (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Research notes, mss. and correspondence: Image Converter, 1939 Oct-Dec (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Research notes and mss. (by title), Em-Z, 1941-1950, undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - "Experiments with a Single Resonator Magnetron," 7 typed pp., 2 copies plus handwritten draft, 7 pp., 1942 Jul (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - "Kurti's Pumping Speed Meter," 2 pp., Undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - "Memorandum on Proposed System for Detecting Thermal Radiation Using Traveling Wave Tubes as R.F. Amplifiers," 3 pp., 1946 Aug (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - "A Method of Detecting an Audio-Frequency Signal in the Presence of Noise by Means of Capillary Waves," 1 p., Undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - "Methods of Using Valves at Very High Frequencies," 10 pp., 1941 Sep (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - "A New Radar System," 15 pp., 1949 Dec (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - "Noise Factor of Receiver," notes for Clarendon Lab talk, 4 pp., 1944 Jun (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - "Note on 'Cooling' of Electron Beams," 4 typed pp., 1950 Nov 21 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - "Search Receiver," 1 p., Undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - "Shot-Noise Compensation at Very High Frequencies," 9 typed pp., Undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - "Source of Noise at Cm-Wave Lengths," 7 pp., Undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - "A Suggestion for a Large-Size Vacuum Chamber," 9 pp., 1945 Sep (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - "Wave Detector Using the Kerr Effect," 3 typed pp., 1945 Jan (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Satellites, misc. information re., Undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Travel arrangements, misc., 1969 Jan-Mar (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Traveling Wave Tubes, correspondence re. patent application and related litigation, 1952 Jul-1953 Sep (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Traveling Wave Tubes, Mss. and patent application, 1948, undated (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Diaries, 1937-1941; Series II
  This series contains one personal diary with many photos from 1937, and several pocket journals dated 1941 and undated.
  - Diary, 1937 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Includes many photographs.
  - Three pocket journals, 1941, undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Notebooks and notes, 1937-1941; Series III
  This series contains notebooks and loose notes on a miscellaneous assortment of topics. Unlike the notes under the heading "Research Notes and Manuscripts" in Series I, or his Bell Telephone Laboratories notebooks in Series IV, these notebooks were l ess systematically kept.
  - Notebook, 1937 Sep-1940 Jan (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Notebook, 1941 Nov-1943 Jun (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Notebook, 1942 Aug-1943 Jun (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Notebook, 1943 Apr-1944 Apr (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Notebook, 1943 Jun-Dec (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Notebook, 1944 Feb-Aug (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Misc. notes, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Misc. notes, 1975-1977 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Pocket notebooks, Undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Notebook, Undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Music notebook, Undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Reprint of Shockley's "Invention of the Transistor ... ", Undated (Box 4, Folder 5a)
- Bell Laboratory notebooks, 1952-1973; Series IV
  These notebooks detail Kompfner's research work at the Bell Telephone Laboratories from 1952 through 1973. The numbers were assigned to the notebooks by Bell Labs.
  - 1952-1956
    - #23834, 1952 Jan 21-Nov 14 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - #24545, 1952 Nov 18-1953 Jun 27 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - #25075, 1953 Jun 30-1954 Jan 24 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - #25584, 1954 Jan 27-Dec 5 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - #264785, 1954 Dec 8-1956 Mar 4 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - 1956-1961
    - #27735, 1956 Mar 5-1957 Apr 28 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - #29092, 1957 Apr 29-Dec 16 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - #29826, 1957 Dec 30-1959 Jan 17 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - #30196, 1959 Jan 25-1960 Mar 22 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - #32458, 1960 Mar 25-Dec 5 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - #33326, 1960 Dec 18-1961 May 15 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - 1961-1966
    - #32868, 1961 May 17-1962 Apr 1 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - #36755, 1962 Apr 17-1963 May 23 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - #38454, 1963 May 26-1964 Mar 18 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - #40359, 1964 Apr 21-Nov 9 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - #41167, 1964 Nov 13-1965 Jun 10 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - #42086, 1965 Jun 10-1966 Feb 2 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - #43243, 1966 Feb 2-May 29 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - 1966-1973
    - #43889, 1966 May 31-Nov 4 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - #44401, 1966 Nov 4-1967 Jul 13 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - #45779, 1967 Jul 14-1968 Jul 23 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - #47582, 1968 Jul 25-1969 Jul 2 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - #48941, 1969 Jul 3-1970 Sep 9 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - #50921, 1970 Oct 4-1971 Oct 7 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - #52151, 1971 Oct 20-1973 May 9 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - #54233, 1973 May 10-Jun 7 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Articles, reports and speeches, 1937-1980; Series V
  This series contains published articles and reports by Kompfner, published articles citing Kompfner and his work, articles autographed by Kompfner, but not written by him, and newsclippings. The series also includes classified reports written by Kompfner in the forties.
  - Articles and reports by Kompfner, 1963-1976
    - The Invention of theTraveling Wave Tube, University of California, Berkeley, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Beitrage zur Erforschung and Nutzbarmachung von Weltraumphanomenen, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Electron Devices in Science and Technology, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Optics at Bell Laboratories, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Responses to 'Optics at Bell Laboratories', 1973 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Recent Advances in Acoustical Microscopy, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - High-Resolution Heterodyne Coincidence Detection of Optical Pulse Streams, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - The Invention of Traveling Wave Tubes, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Mechanical Optrical Fibre Switch, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Classified reports, 1942-1946
    - Experiment related to the Detection of Moving Targets by Doppler Effect, 1945 Jul-Aug (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Notes on the Transmission-Line Noise-Diode, 1946 Feb (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Report on an Investigation of the Distribution of Axial Fields Inside a Helix Excited by Oscillations at Wavelengths comparable with the Diameter of the Helix, 1944 Aug (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Report on a Tube Based on the Traveling Wave Principle, 1944 Jul (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Transit-Line Correction Factor for Cylindrical Noise Diodes, 1945 Sep (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Velocity Modulating Grids, excerpts and correspondence, 1942 Apr (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Articles citing Kompfner, 1937-1973
    - Hauser, Susan G. New Communications Technology, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Pierce, J.F. The Beginnings of Satellite Communication, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Susskind, Charles, Conference on Electron Device Research: a Pattern to be Copied?, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Wright, H. Myles, Small Houses, 1937 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Autographed articles, 1962-1975
    - Dix. C.H. The Present Generation of Traveling Wave Tubes, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Friis, Harold T. 30 Years with Microwaves, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Gabor, D. Laser Speckle and its Elimination, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Keller, Hans Prague Day, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Marsen, Richard Particle Dynamics on a Causal Basis, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Pfann, William G., The Semiconductor Revolution, in William G. Pfann -- Solid State Science and Technology Award Medalist, Journal of the Electrochemical Society, Vol. 121, #1, 1974 Jan (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Science and Engineering, Annual Review for the Industrial Affiliates of Stanford University, 14 pp., 1964 Sep (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Newsclippings, 1960-1980
    - News reports about Kompfner's research, 1960-1980 (Box 9, Folder 22)
- Awards, 1962-1978; Series VI
  This series contains awards, certificates and honorary degrees bestowed upon Kompfner between 1962 and 1978.
  - Rotary Club of Ashbury, New Jersey, Rotary Award, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Rotary Club of Middletown, New Jersey, Certificate of Merit, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Honorary Degree (institution not named), 1969 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Associated Universities Certificate in honor of Kompfner, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Drawings, Undated; Series VII
  This series consits of miscellaneous drawings connected with Kompfner's research.
  - "Transoceanic Communication by Means of Satellite", Undated (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Research drawings, misc., Undated (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Additional Material, 1957-1981; Accession ARCH-1985-074
  - Research files, 1957-1976, undated
    - Allocation of research funds/1, Undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Allocation of research funds/2, Undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Allocation of research funds/3, Undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Allocation of research funds/4, Undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Acoustic microscope - general, Undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Acoustic (harmonic) microscope, Undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Bell Lab Memoranda, 1957-1959 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Bell Lab Memoranda, 1960-1963 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Bell Lab Memoranda, 1964-1967 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Bell Lab Memoranda, 1968-1969 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Bell Lab Memoranda, 1970-1972 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Bell Lab Memoranda, Undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - NAS (National Academy of Sciences) matters, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - NAS - engineering section/1, Undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - NAS - engineering section/2, Undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - NAS - engineering section/3, Undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - NSF ENG74-18437, Undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - NSF ENG74-18437 - financial records, 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Optical fibers research/1, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Optical fibers research/2, Undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Optical fibers research/3, Undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Opto-thermo-acoustic microscope, Undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Picosecond radar proposal/1, Undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Picosecond radar proposal/2, Undated (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Picosecond radar, Undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Range gate based on heterodyne detection, Undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Research notes, Undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Scanning acoustic microscope, 1974-1976 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Schwarzschild II geometry - notes and figures, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Science policy/1, Undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Science policy/2, Undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Towards a domestic communication satellite system, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Research notebooks, 1966-1973
    - Engineering lab, Oxford - notebook, Undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Lab notebook - photocopy, 1966-1967 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Lab notebook - photocopy, 1967-1970 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Lab notebook - photocopy, 1970-1973 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Professional papers, 1952-1977, undated
    - Articles and talks/1, Undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Articles and talks/2, Undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Articles and notes, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Power Travelling-Wave Tubes by J.F. Gittins: book review, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Reguests for reprints, Undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Reprints, Undated (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Reprints, Undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Reprints and articles, Undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Stanford university memoranda and financial records, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Stanford university memoranda and financial records, 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - European trip, 1955 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - European trip, 1955 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, circa 1952-1955 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, circa 1954-1955 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1966-1975 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Epsztein interference case, Undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Epsztein interference case, Undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Patents (applications and correspondence), Undated (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Patents (applications and correspondence), Undated (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Patents (applications and correspondence), Undated (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Patents (applications and correspondence), Undated (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Patents (applications and correspondence), Undated (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Patents, Undated (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Patents, Undated (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous, 1941-1981, undated
    - Oxford University, Undated (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Toft, Louis, Definitions and Formulae for Students, 1941 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - R. Kompfner Memorial Lectures, 1978-1981 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - NOVUS 4510, operations guide, Undated (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Publications (by others, collected by Kompfner): Ashkin to Cutler, Undated (Box 8)
    - Publications (by others, collected by Kompfner): Fox to Goell, Undated (Box 8)
    - Publications (by others, collected by Kompfner): Hargrove to Kogelnik, Undated (Box 8)
    - Publications (by others, collected by Kompfner): Patel to Tynes, Undated (Box 9)
    - Slides from lectures, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Audio tapes, Undated; 2 audiocassette(s) (Box 9)
- Additional Material, 1973-1977, undated; Accession ARCH-1986-125
  - Indexes of publications, awards, patents, biographies, Undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Indexes of publications, awards, patents, biographies, Undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Grant materials/patents lists, Undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - IEEE banquet, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - "Music" - personal reminiscences, Undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Photographs, Undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Notebook, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Notebook, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Notebook, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Notebook, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Notebook, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Notebook, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 3)